(Watch on KonFlix.vip)
Here's the plan for today.
All members of the investigation team,
except Li Qian,
will participate in tonight's operation.
The core members involved in the arrest
will all be armed.
To prevent Mei Dong
from sending someone
to stake out near our station,
we will all
act as usual
[Police]
and get off work in plain clothes.
Once outside,
we will gather at
our respective designated locations.
With Guanlan Hotel as the center,
we will set up surveillance
in all key areas
within a one-kilometer radius.
This will form a comprehensive
and mutually supporting encirclement.
Also, all the hotel's entrances and exits
must be staked out
by experienced officers.
Song Xing,
you are in charge of
keeping an eye on Yang Wei.
After Yang Wei meets with the contact,
if it is confirmed to be Mei Dong,
release the information as planned.
You will lead the team to make the arrest.
If the person who shows up
is just a lackey scouting for Mei Dong,
then stand down.
Understood?
-Understood!
Understood.
Chief Zhang,
is this arrangement okay?
Smooth
and detailed.
Okay, I'll go watch the monitors.
I'll go too.
You rest.
I'll carefully handle the whole thing.
Detailed.
Isn't it the same?
[Born with Luck]
[Episode 14]
[September 7, 2012]
Go.
Reassure him.
Sir, what would you like to drink?
Nothing.
Act like a man.
Our guys are all around here.
Yang Wei?
The room is booked.
Let's go up.
Did you come back with Dong
from Southeast Asia?
Are you guys usually busy?
Is he doing well?
Let's go, Yang.
Dong.
Phone.
What?
It's the rule.
Yang,
we're responsible for Dong's safety.
If anything goes wrong,
we'd be too ashamed
to stay in the business.
You are Dong's friend,
so please understand.
We're doing this
for Dong's own good.
Don't make things difficult
for us subordinates.
Password.
Leave it with me.
What are you doing?
Yang.
Yang,
bear with us.
Come, Yang,
sit down. Come.
Your technique is pretty good.
Where is Dong?
Yang,
Dong tried to contact Lin Kai,
but his phone was turned off.
Later, he called his home,
and his wife said Lin Kai is dead.
Did you know about this?
How did Lin Kai die?
I don't know.
The police
are investigating it, right?
And they refuse to
disclose any details.
All I know is that Kai's body
was found in an empty lot.
From what you're saying,
did the police come to you?
When he had the accident,
he was driving my car.
I shouldn't have lent it to him.
As soon as I lent it to him,
something happened.
Did the police
ask you about anything else,
such as about business?
How could they not ask?
I just kept my mouth shut.
Since they don't have
anything on me,
what could they do to me?
When the time was up, they just let me go.
Hello?
Sir, do you want a massage?
No.
Sir, the spa is on the third floor.
You can come over and try it,
or we can come up.
No need.
Thank you.
Hello?
Okay.
Yang,
let's go.
Where is Dong?
Let's go.
Aren't there elevators here?
[Guest room corridor 4]
Yang,
go in.
Freeze!
Wei.
Don't recognize me?
D-Dong?
I got plastic surgery.
Not as handsome as before, right?
What?
Sit, sit.
Look.
Right.
This is for your mother.
No, I can't.
It's too expensive.
I can't accept this.
We are brothers.
Why are you being so polite?
Is she doing well?
Very well.
That's good.
Why are you being silly?
My appearance has changed,
but my voice hasn't.
Right?
Yes, Dong.
Yes!
Why did you suddenly come back?
For a business deal.
What kind of business
requires such a big risk?
A deal with Zhou Rong.
Think about it.
That's too risky.
Aren't you a wanted man right now?
How is it risky?
I used my passport
and walked openly
through customs.
Dong, the phone.
Sir, do you need a massage?
It would be good to relax a bit.
Dong!
[Guest room corridor 1]
[Guest room corridor 2]
[Guest room corridor 3]
Yang Wei is exposed.
Mei Dong is taking his men
to the emergency stairwell.
Mei Dong is wearing a red hoodie.
Three people in total.
Freeze!
Police!
Stop!
-Freeze!
Dong,
take care.
Wow, resisting arrest.
Look up.
[Photo of Mei Dong, the suspect]
[Wanted]
Is that him?
Captain Wang.
What's wrong with you?
Nothing.
Identify him quickly.
Look up.
This isn't Mei Dong.
Where is Mei Dong?
Search!
Go.
No.
Then I...
You are really a good friend to Dong.
Really?
Police!
[Photo of Mei Dong, the suspect]
Attention all units.
Mei Dong has escaped.
Keep a close eye
on all suspicious persons.
Mei Dong had plastic surgery,
and looks different
from his wanted poster.
Be careful if you spot Mei Dong.
He was once
the Sanda champion of Sanjiangkou.
Hello.
Excuse me,
you look quite different
from the photo.
Are you Mei Dong?
I dare you to let me out!
It really is him.
♪ Snow blankets the Volga River ♪
Attention all units.
Come to the underground loading bay.
♪ Three cars drive over the icy river ♪
Mei Dong has been captured.
This is your overseas phone.
Right?
You used this number
for your MasterCard
and Visa card.
This is your phone.
You can't deny it.
What kind of business are you doing?
[Police]
This is an indictment
found on your computer.
[Civil Complaint]
A foreigner named
Kanokkorn Sukum is going to sue
Zhou Rong's Rongcheng locally
for infringing the patented technology
of rapid concrete hardening
owned by Sumita Company,
which is under her name.
The compensation is 300 million RMB.
Rongcheng
will lose this lawsuit, right?
The 300 million will naturally
flow overseas
as compensation.
You came up with
this money-laundering scheme.
Mei Dong,
using this attitude
towards us is fine.
But I advise you
not to act like this in court.
[Before plastic surgery]
[After plastic surgery]
You laundered the stolen money
from Dinghu's
illegal fundraising case, right?
There are nearly ten thousand victims.
After losing everything,
two jumped off buildings,
and one laid on the tracks.
If the families of the victims
saw you like this...
If you're smart,
confess immediately
and try to get a longer sentence.
For you,
it's safer in jail
than outside.
I can't take it anymore.
I can't.
A genuine smile
is a quarter-second micro-expression.
Anything over five seconds is fake.
You're good.
Aren't your facial muscles tired
after smiling for so long?
Doesn't it ache?
Or is it because of some aftereffects
from your plastic surgery?
[Comparison of Plastic Surgery
Before and After] [Criminal Record]
You really went all out.
Even got it done
in the opposite direction.
The once all-powerful leader
of Jinshuiting
in Sanjiangkou,
you had no choice but to end up like this.
Do you feel a bit wronged?
Who is Kanokkorn?
[Police]
[Personal Information]
She's is the leader of the largest gang
on Sixinlan Island in Southeast Asia.
Their biggest business is
laundering money
for people all over the world.
Mr. Mei
remarried not long after going abroad.
The biggest coincidence is
that his bride is named
Kanokkorn Sukum.
Is that pronunciation correct?
Not bad, yeah?
If my guess is right,
after going abroad,
your money quickly ran out.
When you were at your wits' end,
you happened to meet
this old lady Kanokkorn.
For the sake of wealth
and glory for the rest of his life,
he had no choice but to...
He had no choice.
Mr. Mei is not the boss.
Strictly speaking,
he's just Ms. Kanokkorn's...
Plaything.
With Mr. Mei's
thick eyebrows and big eyes,
would he?
So the one laundering money
is not Mr. Mei.
It's Ms. Kanokkorn.
Now you can understand
why he doesn't dare to confess.
Money laundering
is this gang's
core secret.
If he doesn't confess,
after a few years in prison,
he can go back and live a life of luxury,
accompanying the old lady
in her twilight years.
If he confesses, then...
Stop talking nonsense.
The person who sued
is named Kanokkorn Sukum.
The person I married is named
Kanokkore Sukum.
One ends with an "n."
One ends with an "e."
Thanks a lot.
[Personal Information]
Doesn't look much younger anyway.
What's the relationship
between this Kanokkore
and Kanokkorn?
Is she her
brother's daughter,
sister's daughter,
her own daughter,
or what?
Because at the end of her name,
there is an "e,"
and after her...
She's just my maid!
I used her name
to set up the company.
I married her
just to control the company
behind the scenes.
How could I, Mei Dong,
live off a woman?
I handled all the money laundering
completely by myself.
Since we're on the subject,
just keep talking.
Was the one who approached you
for this business
Zhou Rong?
According to Yang Wei,
[Waiting Area]
this Mei Dong
started with smuggling artifacts.
He's known Liu Bei for a long time.
So earlier,
the bianzhong Zheng Yongbing mentioned
might have been sold by Mei Dong's gang
to Zhou Rong.
It makes perfect sense.
No matter the charge,
as long as Mei Dong exposes Zhou Rong,
we have a reason to investigate him.
Good job.
Keep at it.
[Waiting Area]
[Restricted Caller]
Mr. Rong, are you okay?
Something happened to Mei Dong.
That'll be all.
Chief Zhang, Captain Wang.
Chief Qi asked you to go over immediately.
What's wrong?
You'll know when you get there.
What is it?
What's wrong, Chief Qi?
A little surprise.
Chief Qi said you guys didn't have lunch,
and specifically asked me
to order from outside.
This meal cost Chief Qi...
There's a major breakthrough in the case,
but you guys haven't even eaten.
I'm slacking as the chief.
Sit.
Yi'ang, sit here.
Li Qian,
come.
Ruijun.
Song Xing.
The result might not be
as good as you thought.
Look at you.
I tricked him a bit,
and he fought back immediately.
Why are you
so vindictive?
Come, come.
These are all ordered for you.
Girls like sweet things.
Have some of this.
And this.
Thank you, Chief Qi.
You're welcome.
Chief Qi.
Don't say anything.
Let me say it.
Mei Dong
confessed to the money laundering.
We have
sufficient reasons to file the case.
Right?
And you,
don't eat anything too greasy.
This bitter gourd and pork soup
is good stuff.
You have some too.
This is free-range chicken soup.
Nourish yourself well.
With Zhou Rong's current situation,
are the conditions met for filing a case?
Chief Qi.
I know.
This isn't the most crucial part.
The most crucial part...
Don't you like eating at street stalls?
This mutton,
they said it was slaughtered this morning.
But Song, eat less of this.
The most crucial part
is that once the case is filed,
we can rightfully
investigate Rongcheng.
Am I right?
Mei Dong confessed he was
about to launder money for Zhou Rong.
What do you mean by "about to"?
About to.
It hasn't been implemented yet.
Chief Qi.
If you have any thoughts,
speak up.
Why can't we
take the initiative?
How do we take the initiative?
Find a chance to get close to them.
That's how we can
get evidence of their crimes.
Chief Qi,
Chief Zhang,
Captain Wang.
Have you ever thought about
sending an undercover agent
to infiltrate Zhou Rong's team?
-I think...
-I don't think so.
No way.
Handling cases isn't making movies.
Even based on movie plots,
for someone as cautious as Zhou Rong,
it'll be impossible for the mole
to gain his trust
without a few years' time.
Going undercover won't work.
I interrupted you just now.
What did you say?
I said you're right.
Going undercover won't work.
It's so big.
Chao, it's heavily guarded.
Can we get in?
When my dad remarried,
I supervised the renovation
of the new house.
It was my own dad's wedding.
How could I not do my best?
But even the best-laid plans have flaws.
I forgot to install curtains
in the bedroom.
It was discovered by the neighbors
across the street
on the wedding night.
What did they see?
That's not the point.
My point is,
with so much to worry about,
there will definitely be
things you overlook.
With such a large area,
there are always loopholes.
There must be a way in.
What do you think?
Chao,
when your dad remarried,
what did the neighbor across the street
see?
You can't explain ice to a summer insect.
What do you mean?
What do you mean, Chao?
Chao?
Are you mad?
I'm sorry, okay?
Let's go around the back and take a look.
♪ Bunny, bunny, bunny, bunny,
bunny, bunny ♪
♪ Love you, love you, love you ♪
♪ Bunny, bunny, bunny, bunny,
bunny, bunny ♪
♪ Love you, love you, love you ♪
♪ Oh Gimme ♪
♪ Dance me in the richness ♪
♪ Raining make it rain ♪
♪ Oh cash is my revolution ♪
♪ Get your head in the game,
we're all smart people here ♪
♪ Don't drag your feet,
even gold slips through slow hands ♪
♪ I beat it, I beat it ♪
Look.
Help me up!
Pull harder!
Pull me!
Chao, what do we do now?
Everyone,
let's groove!
Mr. Rong!
Zhu Yifei has arrived at Sanjiangkou.
But he wants to
hold off on the deal
for a couple of days.
Hold off?
Very good.
Let's speed up the tempo!
Wait.
Who does he think he is?
I paid the money.
Why does he get to hold off?
Tell him to go ask
who owns Sanjiangkou.
[Restricted Number]
Give it to me.
Hello.
Mr. Zhu,
this is Zhou Rong.
Keep up with the music.
Let's groove!
Come on.
Hello,
can you hear me?
It's Zhou Rong!
Speed up.
Faster.
Hello?
Speed up.
Stop.
Stop!
No, I said stop the music.
Music.
Hello.
Hold off, my ass!
Are you alright, Mr. Rong?
I'm fine.
If he needs time, let him have it.
With how smart Zhu Yifei is,
he won't do anything
to get himself killed.
Pass the word.
Don't do anything for the next two days.
Don't cause any trouble.
Reassure him.
Yes.
And
Mei Dong was caught by the police.
I don't know
what he told Zhang Yi'ang.
Right now, the police
might already be onto us.
So...
watch out.
I will definitely be careful
and keep a low profile.
No,
just act as usual,
understand?
Jianren,
I'll be honest with you.
If East New Town's loan
doesn't come through
and the police target us too,
I plan to
leave Sanjiangkou.
But don't worry.
I will take you with me.
Where
would we go?
A small island in the South Pacific,
my utopia,
Gondwana.
Gondwana?
Let's eat first.
We have to investigate,
but we also have to eat.
Your brain works faster after a meal.
Yi'ang,
take the lead.
Let's eat.
Do you have any staple food there?
I was only thinking about
the dishes Chief Qi asked me to order,
and forgot the staple food.
Go get some staple food quickly.
Forgot to order staple food.
Young people are careless.
Forgetting to order staple food
is not a big deal.
It's not a big deal,
but it's the small things
that give you away.
Zhou Rong
is very careful.
But that doesn't mean
everyone around him
will be careful.
You mean
to expand the surveillance range?
Right.
You're right.
We need to find a chance to approach them.
Hu Jianren is
Zhou Rong's trusted aide.
Li Qian,
starting tomorrow,
you keep an eye on Hu Jianren.
I'll keep an eye on Li Penggai.
What did you say?
He said he'll go keep an eye
on Li Penggai.
Okay, you keep an eye on Li Penggai.
Chief Qi, I suggest
we split into more groups.
Keep a close eye on all the key people
around Zhou Rong.
If we can catch just one,
we can track down the rest
and make a breakthrough.
Okay.
Let's eat first.
I'm finally back.
Stop.
Goodbye, brother.
Driver, go on!
Gai.
You were supposed to hand in your computer
when you left.
[Du Cong, staff of Zhou Rong's company]
I didn't let them.
I told them not to touch it,
or else Gai would make life hard
for all of them
when he came back.
You're the best.
The best bro.
Is your promotion
confirmed?
Confirmed or not,
I won't be staying here for long anyway.
Gai,
is the company's S600
being used these days?
We have so many cars. Why use that one?
Did Li ask to borrow a car again?
Not again.
This is the first time.
I know, Gai.
It's not the right time yet.
Say no more.
It's not easy for Li
to run a wedding company.
You two finally started dating.
How can you not lend her a car
when she asks?
Lend it.
Mr. Rong has so many cars.
He won't mind one less. Lend it.
Gai.
Hey, hey,
what are you doing?
What are you doing?
Stand up.
Look at you.
Take it.
Drive safely.
Thanks, Gai.
Give me two servings of meat dumplings.
And then?
Eggs...
Give me three eggs.
Here, three for you.
Need anything else?
Get me some milk.
I paid you.
Thanks.
A milk too.
I don't drink that.
Not that one. This one.
Sure thing.
Take care.
What are you honking for?
No manners.
Shy.
S-H-Y.
Hu Jianren didn't go to the company.
I repeat,
[Sanjiangkou Children's Training Center]
This is a little girl.
-This is a little girl.
And she has a little curl.
-And she has a little curl.
-And when she is bad...
She is very, very bad.
-She is...
-She is very, very bad.
What's wrong?
I want to go to WC.
No, no, no, listen to me.
I want to go to toilet.
I want go to toilet.
Toilet.
Toi...
Teacher, it's urgent.
Go ahead.
Thank you.
This is the children's center.
There are only kids taking classes inside.
Who is he going to meet here?
Keep watching.
There must be something wrong.
He is a bit shy.
-He is a bit shy.
Bit.
Halt.